[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":108461,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":325880,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":5629,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":331511,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":9013,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":340528,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1496113,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":1836642,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":9942,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":1846585,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":4911,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":1851497,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number , and th en add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3582,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":1855081,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1150,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":1856233,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5543,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":1861777,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":2414,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":1864192,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2671,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":1866865,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1230,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":1868096,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3439,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":1871536,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":975,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":1872512,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"W hat is 1  +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2111,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":1874625,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":881,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":1875506,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger , you su btract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2069,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":1877576,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":727,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":1878304,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2191,"trial_type":"quest ion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":1880496,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":751,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":1881248,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":1807,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":1883056,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":933,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":1883991,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":12230,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":1896225,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6 </sub>).  Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":46285,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":1942511,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5422,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":1947934,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1135,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":1949071,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the  inverse  of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3447,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":1952518,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":911,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":1953430,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":1977,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":1955408,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1493,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":1956902,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2247,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":1959150,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub >6</sub>  4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":815,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":1959966,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":17790,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":1977758,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3008,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":1980766,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively ap ply +<su b>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":52484,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":2033250,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6< /sub> 2,  and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":217198,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":2250450,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":6926,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":2257378,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":4351,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":2261730,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.1 0-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":4159,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":2265890,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":2855,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":2268746,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":2327,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":2271074,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1447,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":2272522,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":3415,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":2275938,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":2215,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":2278154,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce num bers bet ween 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":19630,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":2297785,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4783,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":2302569,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1191,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":2303761,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":4422,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":2308185,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":8878,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":2317065,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4543,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":2321608,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":7015,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":2328625,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4","3"],"rt":5252,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":2333880,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":11279,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":2345159,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"4 plus 1 is less than 9, so there's no reason to make a difference of 9.","explanation_history":["4 plus 1 is less than 9, so there's no reason to e","4 plus 1 is less than 9, so there's no reason to subtract ","4 plus 1 is less than 9, so there's no reason to s","4 plus 1 is less than 9, so there's no reason to make a difference of 9."],"response_history":["4","5"],"rt":44069,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":2389230,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"8 plus 4 i s 12, wh ich is more than 9, so 12 minus 9 is 3.","explanation_history":["8 +","8 plus 4 is 12, which is more tabn ","8 plus 4 is 12, which is more tabn","8 plus 4 is 12, which is more tab","8 plus 4 is 12, which is more tah","8 plus 4 is 12, which is more ta","8 plus 4 is 12, which is more than 9, so 12 minutes ","8 plus 4 is 12, which is more than 9, so 12 minutes","8 plus 4 is 12, which is more than 9, so 12 minute","8 plus 4 is 12, which is more than 9, so 12 minut","8 plus 4 is 12, which is more than 9, so 12 minu","8 plus 4 is 12, which is more than 9, so 12 minus 9 is 3."],"response_history":["3"],"rt":31470,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":2420701,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"1","explain":true,"explanation":"Because 1 can make every other element  under + 9.","explanation_history":["Because 1 can make every other element under +6, we say that 1 is a generator under +6","Because 1 can make every other element under +9, we say that 1 is a generator under +6","Because 1 can make every other element under +9,","Because 1 can make every other element under +9."],"response_history":["1"],"rt":76717,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":2497419,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":13428,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":2510851,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":2710,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":2513563,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":2455,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":2516019,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"6 is the opposite number of 3 to make the answer 9.","explanation_history":["6 is the opposite ","6 is the opposite","6 is the oppositt ","6 is the oppositt","6 is the opposite numbe rof","6 is the opposite numbe ro","6 is the opposite  numbe r ","6 is the opposite numbe ","6 is the opposite number of 3 to make the answer 0","6 is the opposite number of 3 to make the answer 9."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":24213,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":2540234,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"There's no way to make 9 using just 2. ","explanation_history":["Ther i","Ther ","There ","Ther's n","Ther's ","Ther's","Ther'","There's no way to make 89 ","There's no way to make 89","There's no way to make 8","There's no way to make 9 using just 2. "],"response_history":["No"],"rt":67020,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":2607256,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please  explain  in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"You can make every other number with 3. ","explanation_history":["You cam make ","You cam make","You cam mak","You cam ma","You cam m","You cam ","You cam","You can make every othe rnum","You can make every othe rnu","You can make every othe rn","You can make every othe r","You can make every othe ","You can make every other number with 3. "],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":38818,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":2646075,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"There's no way to make some of the other numbers with just 5.","explanation_history":["There's no  way to  make some of the othr n","There's no way to make some of the othr ","There's no way to make some of the othr","There's no way to make some of the other numbers with just 5."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":12024,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":2658100,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"There's no way to make some of the other numbers with just 6. ","explanation_history":["There's no way to make some of the other numbres iwth ","There's no way to make some of the other numbre","There's no way to make some of the other numbr","There's no way to make some of the other numb","There's no way to make some of the other numers","There's no way to make some of the other numer","There's no way to make some of the other  nume"," There's no way to make some of the other numbers iwth j","There's no way to make some of the other numbers iwth ","There's no way to make some of the other numbers iwth","There's no way to make some of the other numbers iwt","There's no way to make some of the other numbers iw","There's no way to make some of the other numbers i","There's no way to make some of the other numbers with just 6. "],"response_history":["No"],"rt":22261,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":2680364,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":167130,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2847495,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"I honestly have no idea, I'm sorry.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I honestly have no idea, I'm sorry."],"rt":64115,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2911611,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I don't know","explain":true,"explanation":"I'm sorry... did you explain this to me? I read the little blurb you gave me just before these problems, but it didn't say anything about a formula. ","explanation_history":["I don' r","I don' ","I don't kno","I'm sorry...d id y","I'm sorry...d id ","I'm sor ry...d id","I'm sorry...d i","I'm sorry...d ","I'm sorry...d","I'm sorry... did you explain this to me? I read the little bur","I'm sorry... did you explain this to me? I read the little bu","I'm sorry... did you explain this to me? I read the little blurb you gave me just before these problems, but it didn't say anything about a formula. "],"response_history":["I don't kno2","I don't know"],"rt":45758,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2957370,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, X has to make every other element under +n. But that sounds like gibberish to me without any actual numbers to plug in.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Thats' what","Thats' wha","Thats' wh","Thats' w","Thats' ","Thats'","Thats","That is what *I* would like to know! 1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! I1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In 1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In o1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In or1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In ord1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order 1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order o 1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order o t1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order o tb e1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I * would  like to know! In order o tb 1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order o tb1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order o t1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order o 1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order o1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order t1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to 1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be 1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a 1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a je1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I*  would l ike to know! In order to be a j1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a g1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a ge1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a gene1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a gener1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a genera1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generat1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generato1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, 1 can make every other element under ","That is what *I* wo uld like  to know! In order to be a generator,  can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, th can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, the  can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, the n can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, the nu can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, the num can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, the number can make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, the number an make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, the number a make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like t o know!  In order to be a generator, the number  make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, the number has make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, the number has  make every other element under ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, the number has to make every other element under +n. ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, X has to make every other element under +n. But this sou","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, X has to make every other element under +n. But this so","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, X has to make every other element under +n. But this s","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, X has to make every other element under +n. But this ","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, X has to m ake ever y other element under +n. But this","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, X has to make every other element under +n. But thi","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, X has to make every other element under +n. But that sounds likge","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, X has to make every other element under +n. But that sounds likg","That is what *I* would like to know! In order to be a generator, X has to make every other element under +n. But that sounds like gibberish to me without any actual numbers to plug in."],"rt":98508,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":3055879,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":10701,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":3066582,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True","False"],"rt":9407,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":3075990,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":11343,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":3087333,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"False","explain":true,"explanation":"It's false because we don't know what numbers you're actually talking about, and they could behave differently depending on what you do with them.","explanation_history":["It's false because t","It's false because w","It's false because e","It's false because we don't know wha tnu","It's false because we don't know wha tn","It's false because we don't know wha t","It's false because we don't know wha ","It's false because we don't know what numbers you're actually talking about, and they could p","It's false because we don't know what numbers you're actually talking about, and they could behave differently dependin go n","It's  false because we don't know what numbers you're actually talking about, and they could behave differently dependin go","It's false because we don't know what numbers you're actually talking about, and they could behave differently dependin g","It's false because we don't know what numbers you're actually talking about, and they could behave differently dependin ","It's false because we don't know what numbers you're actually talking about, and they could behave differently depending on what you do with them."],"response_history":["False"],"rt":41020,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":3128355,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":11759,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":3140115,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if X is a generator. It sometimes is and it sometimes isn't. ","explanation_history":["Since I don't know wthe n","Since I don't know wthe ","Since I don't know wthe","Since I don't know wth","Since I don't know wt","Since I don't know w","Since I don't know the numbers ","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if the elem","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sur e either  way if the ele","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if the el","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if the e","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if the ","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if the","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if th","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if t","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if X is a g","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if X is a ","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if X is age","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if X is ag","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if X is a generator, so it ","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if X is a generator, so it","Since I don't know the numbers, I  can't s ay for sure either way if X is a generator, so i","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if X is a generator, so ","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if X is a generator, so","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if X is a generator, s","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if X is a generator, ","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if X is a generator,","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if X is a generator. It sometimes is and it sim","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if X is a generator. It sometimes is and it si","Since I don't know the numbers, I can't say for sure either way if X is a generator. It sometimes is and it sometimes isn't. "],"response_history":["Sometimes","Sometimes"],"rt":55686,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":3195802,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":4358,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":3200161,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1534,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":3201697,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"42","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["42"],"rt":2319,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":3204017,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Associates Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Associates Degree"],"rt":3024,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":3207041,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"college algebra... I never went any further, and that was 20 years ago. ","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I only got as far as cl","I only got as far as college algebra... I never went any fot","I only got as far as college algebra... I never went any fo","I only got as far as college algebra... I never went any further, and that was 20 years","I only got as far as college algebra... I never went any further, and that was 20 year","I only got as far as college algebra... I never went any further, and that was 20 yea","I only got as far as college algebra... I never went any further, and that was 20 ye","I only got as far as college algebra... I never went any further, and that was 20 y","I only got as far as college algebra... I never went any further, and that was 20 ","I only got as far as college algebra... I never went any further, and that was 20 years ago.","college algebra... I never went any further, and that was 20 years ago."],"rt":35581,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":3242624,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":6047,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":3248672,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 -  never h eard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3246,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":3251919,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3239,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":3255160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat","1 - not at  all","2  - somewhat","1 - not at all"],"rt":14640,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":3269800,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":4118,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":3273920,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":1950,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":3275872,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The langua ges spok en in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":4016,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":3279888,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No... perhaps I should have. Sorry.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No, ","No,","No... perhaps I shoul hav","No... perhaps I shoul ha","No... perhaps I shoul h","No... perhaps I shoul ","No... perhaps I should ave,","No... perhaps I should ave","No... perhaps I should av","No... perhaps I should a","No... perhaps I should have, though","No... perhaps I should have, thoug","No... perhaps I should have, thou","No... perhaps I should have, tho ","No...  perhaps I should have, th","No... perhaps I should have, t","No... perhaps I should have, ","No... perhaps I should have,","No... perhaps I should have. Sorry."],"rt":16469,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":3296359,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm really, truly sorry I didn't perform very well on this task. I tried my best but some of the concepts were a little over my head. Thank you for letting me try, though!","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I'm really, truly sorry I didn't f","I'm really, truly sorry I didn't perform very well on this task. I d","I'm really, truly sorry I didn't perform very well on this task. I tried my best but someo fo t","I'm really, truly sorry I didn't perform very well on this task. I tried my best but someo fo ","I'm really , truly  sorry I didn't perform very well on this task. I tried my best but someo fo","I'm really, truly sorry I didn't perform very well on this task. I tried my best but someo f","I'm really, truly sorry I didn't perform very well on this task. I tried my best but someo ","I'm really, truly sorry I didn't perform very well on this task. I tried my best but someo","I'm really, truly sorry I didn't perform very well on this task. I tried my best but some of the cfoncep","I'm really, truly sorry I didn't perform very well on this task. I tried my best but some of the cfonce","I'm really, truly sorry I didn't perform very well on this task. I tried my best but some of the cfonc","I'm really, truly sorry I didn't perform very well on this task. I tried my best but some of the cfon","I'm really, truly sorry I didn't perform very well on this task. I tried my best but some of the cfo","I'm really, truly sorry I didn't perform very well on this task. I tried my best but some of the cf","I' m really , truly sorry I didn't perform very well on this task. I tried my best but some of the concepts were a little over my head. Thank you four lett","I'm really, truly sorry I didn't perform very well on this task. I tried my best but some of the concepts were a little over my head. Thank you fou","I'm really, truly sorry I didn't perform very well on this task. I tried my best but some of the concepts were a little over my head. Thank you for letting me try, though!"],"rt":27165,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":3323526,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]